"在我们的感官背后,绝对有可能
隐藏着不为我们所知的新世界"
新世界
恶魔!
Diablos!
怪物猎人
[可口可乐]
我们的世界
联合国联合安全行动
纬度33°56’2.54”N
经度67°42’12.35”E
主猎鹰,这是B队.
Falcon Main, this is Bravo Team.
主猎鹰,这是B队.你听到吗?
Do you copy?
暴风雨来了.可见度为零.请立即支援.
Storm incoming. Zero visibility.
Request immediate support.
主猎鹰,有某些东西和我们一起.
请立即支援.
Falcon Main, something's in here with us.
Send immediate support.
主猎鹰,这是B队.请立即支援.
Falcon Main, this is Bravo Team.
Send immediate support.
队长.
Ma'am. Ma'am.
-马歇尔.
-林克在前面半公里处有所发现.
- Marshall.
- Link found something half a klick ahead.
-是B队吗?
-我认为是他们.
- Bravo Team?
- Think so.
艾克斯...
Axe.
-跟着斯蒂勒.负责机关枪.
-是的,队长.
- With Steeler. Man the 50.
- Yes, boss.
好了,女士们.
All right, ladies.
出发.
Saddle up.
她是女人但她的语气还是像羞辱人.
She's a woman, but she still manages
to make that sound like an insult.
习惯就好.
Get used to it.
队长.
Captain.
你看到这些里程碑吗?
You see those markers?
是的.我看到了.
Yeah, I see them.
你知道这些是什么吗?
Do you have any idea what they are?
戴维斯中士,
我是游骑兵,不是考古学家.
Sergeant Davis, I'm a Ranger,
not an archeologist.
收到.
Copy that.
艾克斯!
Axe!
什么?
What?
你在听什么?
What are you listening to?
乔治琼斯.
George Jones.
谁?
Who the hell's that?
斯蒂勒,你很庸俗.
You're a philistine, Steeler.
我是.
Yes. Yes, I am.
马歇尔, 你的反应很快.
Damn, Marshall. You got hella reflexes.
今天第十五个伤亡.
Fifteenth casualty today.
-杀光他们.
-戴维斯,不要留活口.
- Killing them.
- Take no prisoners, Davis.
-林克,你发现什么?
-肯定是B队.
- Link, what'd you find?
- It's definitely Bravo Team.
但它的踪迹到此为止.
But the tracks end here.
-B队乘什么到达这里?
-悍马武装车和马特-V.
- What were Bravo Team traveling in?
- Up-armored Humvee and a M-ATV.
那是10吨装甲车.不可能就这样消失.
That's ten tons of armored vehicle.
They don't just disappear.
队长.我们有所发现.
Boss, we've got something.
小心.十二点钟方向.
Incoming. On your 12.
-它们从那里来?
-突然出现.
- Where did that come from?
- Came out of nowhere.
B队在最后一次报告说遇到了风暴.
Bravo Team reported a storm
in their last transmission.
-敌方使用它作掩护?
-埋伏.好像在赫尔曼德吗?
- Hostiles using it for cover?
- An ambush. Like in Helmand?
我不想知道.
Let's not find out.
准备袭击.
REDCON-1.
如果有敌人躲在风暴后面,
情况会很危险.
If there are hostiles hiding
behind that storm, things might get kinetic.
收到.
Copy that.
马歇尔,你在干嘛?
Marshall, what are you doing, bro?
如果我的头被轰掉...
In case I get my head blown off,
他们还记得我是谁.
they can still tell who I am.
非常恶劣,混蛋.
Hardcore shit, cabrón.
Damn!
我的天,差一点.
Goddamn, that shit's close.
林克!你有看过这种闪电吗?
Link, you ever seen lightning
like this before?
从来没有.
No. Never.
但是我觉得在这个大铁盒里...
But I feel pretty secure here
in this big steel box,
拿着我的金属枪很安全.
holding my metal gun.
戴斯!你的十二点方向!
Dash, on your 12!
看那些里程碑!
Look at those markers!
什么东西?
What the hell is that?
-小心!
-该死的!
- Watch out!
- Damn it!
抓稳!
Brace yourselves!
Shit!
我们在那里?
Where the hell are we?
暴风雨发生了什么事?
And what happened to the storm?
刚才发生什么事?
What the hell just happened?
-嗨!
-大伙们!
- Hey!
- Guys!
你还好吗?
You okay?
我还没死.
I'll survive.
我们被闪电击中了吗?
Did we just get hit by lightning?
-斯蒂勒,你还好吗?
-我没事.
- Steeler, you good?
- Never better.
这些沙从哪里来?
Where did all this sand come from?
这不对.一切都很奇怪.
This isn't right, none of it.
那是什么?
What the hell is that?
我没看到地图上有任何建筑物或山脉.
I don't see any structures or mountains
marked on this map.
根据这里...
According to this,
最近的沙丘在20公里外.
the nearest sand dune is 20 klicks away.
-这怎么可能?
-我们在那里?
- How's that possible?
- Where the hell are we?
-我们怎么离开道路那么远?
-我不清楚.
- How did we get so far from the road?
- I don't know.
艾克斯,
爬上其中一个沙丘和设立观察点.
Axe, get on one of those dunes
and set up an observation point.
遵命.
Yes, boss.
斯蒂勒!
Steeler!
甲车还能动.它之前遇过更糟糕的情况.
DPV will run. She's had worse.
-马歇尔?
-队长,全球定位系统坏了.
- Marshall?
- GPS is fried, boss.
收音机和卫星电话没动静.
Radio and sat. All I get is static.
连指南针也坏了.一定是被雷击.
Even the compass is screwed up.
Must have been the lightning.
你想怎么做?
Well, what do you wanna do?
换模拟.靠太阳导航.
Go analog. Navigate by the sun.
回去基地.如果必须的话,我们步行.
Make it back to base.
We hoof it if we have to.
队长,那很遥远.
Boss, that's a long hike.
我们一直步行直到恢复通讯.
Yeah, well,
we keep going till we get comms.
AWACS将派出支援.
他们会派直升机或装甲车.
Then AWACS will call in support.
They'll send helos, maybe armor.
-很好.
-我们继续吧.
- Nice.
- Back in business.
队长...
Boss.
-说.
-有些东西你必须看.
- Send it.
-There's something you got to see.
武装DPV和马特-V.
Up-armored DPV and a M-ATV.
B队.
It's Bravo Team.
V队形.走吧.
V-formation. Move out.
我们如何处理他们?
What do we do about them?
恢复通讯后,
我们会通知回收队来取尸体.
When we get comms, we'll call in
recovery assets to retrieve the bodies.
-他们发生了什么事?
-喷火器.
- What happened to them?
- Flamethrowers.
我不这么认为.
I don't think so.
从未见过喷火器会造成人这样.
Never seen a flamethrower
do this to a man.
甚至凝固汽油也不是那么烫.
Not even napalm burns that hot.
队长...
Ma'am?
是玻璃.
It's glass.
玻璃?
Glass?
沙子融化后变成玻璃.
When sand melts, it turns to glass.
如何融化沙子?
How do you melt sand?
我不知道.
I don't know.
这超越我的职权范围.
This shit is officially above
my pay grade.
好像他们有打斗.
Looks like they made a stand.
开了很多枪.
Let off a lot of rounds.
但没有射中目标.
They didn't hit anything.
没有尸体.
There's no bodies.
也许他们带走尸体?
Maybe they took the bodies with them?
我以前看过这样的情形.
I've seen that before.
这就是问题.
Yeah.Well, that's just the thing.
林克,你看到什么东西?
What do you see, Link?
什么都没看到.
Nothing.
到处都没有痕迹.
No tracks anywhere.
不管是谁干的,他们没有留下痕迹.
Whoever did this,
they didn't leave a mark.
我们必须继续走.出发!
We need to get moving. Move out!
暗星呼叫猎鹰,请回答.
Dark Star to Falcon.
Dark Star to Falcon, over.
该死,电击破坏所有电子产品.
Damn it. Lightning really messed up
the electronics, huh?
不但是电子产品.
Not just electronics.
-什么意思?
-有什么不妥?
- What do you mean?
- This isn't right.
全部都不妥.
Nothing about this is right.
那闪电...对我们做了一些事情.
That lightning, it did something to us.
队长知道她在做什么,好吗?
Captain knows what she's doing, all right?
他们说当兵会富有
They say that in the army
The pay is mighty fine
他们说当兵会富有
They say that in the army
The pay is mighty fine
他们给了100拿回99
They give a hundred dollars
And take back 99
他们给了100拿回99
They give a hundred dollars
And take back 99
哦,我想走
Oh, how I wanna go
但是他们不给走
But they won't let me go
回家
Home
他们说兵鞋很酷
They say that in the army
The shoes are mighty fine
你要11号,他们给你9号
You ask for size 11
They give you size nine
你要11号,他们给你9号
You ask for size 11
They give you a size nine
天啊,我要走但是他们不给走
Oh, Lord, I wanna go
But they won't let me go
Home
天啊.
Jesus.
这一定是恐龙,对吗?
It has to be a dinosaur, right?
有一次在博物馆里看到恐龙.
Saw a dinosaur in a museum one time.
但没有那么大.
It wasn't that big.
敌人,12点方向.300米外.
Hostile, 12 o'clock, 300 meters!
停火!
Cease fire! Cease fire!
发生什么事?
What's going on?
只是粉.
It's just chalk.
队长!
Chief?
角龙.
Diablos.
在我们的六点!
On our 6!
什么东西?
What the hell is that?
林克!上车.
Link, back in the vehicle.
戴斯,斯蒂勒,快走!
Dash, Steeler, move, move, move!
开枪!
Fire!
它越来越靠近我们!
It's gaining on us!
你被包围了.
You're caught.
-快离开这里!
-不行!
- Come on, get out of here!
- No way!
- 一...
-我的天...
- One...
- Holy...
二,三.
...two, three!
开枪!
Fire!
快给我你的手!
Give me your hand. Come on!
戴斯!快点!
Dash! Come on!
我正在努力!
I'm trying!
斯蒂勒!
Steeler!
行了!
Got it, got it, got it!
马歇尔!上车!
Marshall, get in!
快,大个子!
Let's go, big boy!
手给我.
Give me your hand!
进去.
Get inside!
林克!拿火箭炮!
Link, get the RPG!
我的天.
Oh, my God.
撤退!
Fall back!
撤退!找掩护!
Fall back! Run for cover!
队长!
Captain.
快.
Come on!
快来,老板.
Come on, boss!
我来挡住它!快走!
I got it, I got it! Move, move!
重装子弹!
Reloading!
那是什么东西?
What was that thing? What is that?
我说过那团光会带我们去某处.
I told you. I told you.
That light, it took us somewhere.
我们必须回去.
We need to get back.
We need to get back home.
-冷静 戴维斯军士.
-我的天,我们会死在这里.
- Stow it, Sergeant Davis.
- Oh, my God. We're gonna die here.
你给我闭嘴,士兵,那是命令.
Shut that shit up right now, soldier.
That's an order.
你看到它对斯蒂勒和艾克斯
做了什么吗?
You see what it did to Steeler and Axe?
戴斯.我有三个.你呢?
Dash, hey. I got three. You?
-什么?
-三盒子弹.
- What?
- Three mags left.
重要吗?你看到那东西吗?
What does it matter? Did you see that?
重要因为我们是军人
而我们的工作就是战斗
It matters because we're soldiers.
And this is what we do. We fight.
-对吗?
-游骑兵带路.
- Am I right?
- Rangers lead the way.
-你跟我去吗?
-一直都是,老板.
- You with me?
- Always, boss.
你们全都疯了.
You're all crazy.
我不管那是什么东西.
You know, I don't care
what the hell that thing is.
我们做我们最擅长的事.
我们战斗和活下来.
We do what we do best.
We fight and we survive.
不管有多大机会.明白吗?
No matter what the odds. You got it?
-遵命.
- Yes, ma'am.
明白吗?
You got it?
清楚,长官.
Loud and clear, ma'am.
我只剩下三盒.你呢?
Now, I got three left. What about you?
药物包!
Med pack!
-CPR,马歇尔.
-好.
- CPR, Marshall.
- On it.
-太迟了.
-胡说!
- It's too late.
- Bullshit!
别死,游骑兵.加油!
Don't die on me, Ranger. Come on.
-没心跳.
-不能接受.再尝试.
- Lack of pulse.
- Unacceptable. Try it again.
-对不起.
-天啊!还有更多!
- I'm sorry.
- Shit! There's more of them!
快!我们要走了!
Come on! We have to go!
它们无所不在!
They're everywhere!
-对不起.
-军士长!
-I'm sorry.
-Master sergeant!
-林克!
-好,跟我走!
- Link!
- All right, on me!
我们退后!
Let's move out!
撤退!
Fall back, fall back!
戴斯!
Dash!
-来!
-继续走!
Come on! Keep moving!
马歇尔!
Marshall!
快走!
Go, go, go!
林克.
Link.
戴斯.
Dash.
[马歇尔 史蒂文]
[药物包]
[呼吸氧气]
拜托.
Come on.
-你还活着.
-林克.
- You're alive.
- Link.
是什么?
What is it? What is it?
我的胸口很痛.
Pain in my chest!
感觉不到我的手臂.
I can't feel my arm.
是某种毒.
Some sort of poison.
你必须撑住.
You just gotta work through it.
来.走吧.
Come on. Let's move. Come on.
All right.
天啊.
Oh, God.
糟了.
Oh, no.
队长.
Captain.
好了,再走一点.走吧.
All right, it's just a little further.
Let's go.
我不能动.
I can't move.
好,让我看看是什么.
Okay, let me see.
Let me see what it is.
走!
Go!
我的天!
Oh, my God!
-天啊!林克!不要!
-你必须走!
-God, Link! No!
-You gotta go!
林克!
Link!
永远
Damn you.
Damn you!
但是我会回来.
But I'm coming home.
尼西拉.
Nerscylla.
-尼西拉.
-放开我!
- Nerscylla!
- Get off me.
你过得真好...
Nice life you've...
让你受受看.
See how you like it.
干杯.
Cheers.
你这小混蛋.
Oh, you spiteful little bastard.
嘿,不如砸烂那个?
Hey. How about that?
你不喜欢吗?现在没那么好笑了吗?
Yeah. You don't like that, huh?
Not so funny now, huh?
我会杀了你.
I'll kill you.
来!
Come on!
往上推!
Push! Push!
拿去.
Here.
我不是你的敌人.
I'm not your enemy.
等一等.
Wait, wait.
Wait.
一会.
One second.
看.
Look. Look.
给你.
Here.
食物.
Food.
食物.拿去.
Food. Here.
拿着.
Take it.
给我.看.
Here, give it to me.
Look, look.
真美味.
So good.
很美味,对吗?
It's good, right?
哇.
慢点.好.它很美味.
Slow down. Okay, it's good.
这是巧克力.
It's chocolate.
巧克力.
Chocolate.
是的,巧克力.
Yeah, chocolate.
巧克力.
Chocolate.
巧克力!
- Choco...
- Chocolate!
我没有了.
- I don't have any more.
没有了.看.没有了.
No, no more, no more, no more.
Look, look. Nothing.
对不起.
I'm sorry.
我的天.谢谢你.
Oh, my God. Thank you so much.
我的天.
Oh, my God.
谢谢.
Thank you.
嘿!
Hey.
等一等!你要去哪里?
Wait! Where are you going?
等一等!
Wait!
我和你出去那里吗?
Me and you go out there?
是的.
Yes.
我想是那闪电带我来这里.
That lightning,
I think that's what brought me here.
我必须回去那里.我必须回家.
I need to go there. I need to get home.
那东西还在那里.
That thing is still out there.
角龙.
Diablos.
嘿,那边...
Hey, over there...
我有武器.
I have weapons.
角龙...
Diablos...
什么?
What?
Ni trovi Nerscylla.
什么?
What?
尼西拉.
Nerscylla.
不.
No.
我们不必回去那里.
We don't need to go back in there.
我们必须出去那里.角龙.
We need to go out there. Diablos.
-角龙.
-Diablos.
内色拉.
Nerscylla.
角龙.
Diablo...
我们毒死它.
We poison it.
聪明.
Smart.
要杀一只怪物,你需要另一只怪物.
To kill a monster, you need a monster.
但是我们要如何捉到它?
But how are we gonna get
one of those things?
什么?
What?
他们说在军中咖啡是最棒的
They say that in the army
The coffee's mighty fine
它像泥水味道像松节油
It looks like muddy water
And tastes like turpentine
天啊,我要走但是他们不给走
Oh, Lord, I wanna go
But they don't let me go
Home
他们说军中男人很强
They say that in the army
The men are mighty fine
我觉得他们像驼子,声音像科学怪人
To me they look like hunchbacks
And sound like Frankenstein
天啊,我要走但是他们不给走
Oh, Lord, I wanna go
But they won't let me go
Home
来吧!
Come on!
好.拿到了!
Yes! Got it!
下次你做饵!
Next time, you're bait!
[游骑兵]
"游骑兵".
"Ranger."
那是我.
That's me.
游骑兵.
Ranger.
是的.
Yeah. Yeah.
猎人.
Hunter.
猎人.游骑兵.
Hunter. Ranger.
-是的.
-猎人?
- Yeah.
- Hunter?
是的.
Yes.
魔术贴.
Velcro.
魔术贴?
是的.
Yeah.
魔术贴.
Velcro. Velcro.
好了.够了.
Okay. All right, all right.
That's enough. That's enough.
天啊.
Oh, man.
真的想进来这里吗?
Really trying to get in here, huh?
那是你的家人吗?
Is that your family?
你要去见他们吗?你要回家吗?
Are you gonna see them?
Are you gonna go home?
回家?
Home?
对不起.
I'm sorry.
雄火龙.
Rathalos.
我们干吧.
Let's do this.
算了.我们走吧.
Never mind. Let's go.
准备!
Ready!
好!
Yeah!
哇.
那是什么?你必须告诉我.
What is that?
You gotta tell me about that.
你不能随便这样作弄人.
You can't just do that to somebody.
随时开始.
Any second now.
停!
Stop!
饵!
Bait!
好!
Shit!
[JSO求生营]
醒醒!
Come on!
保佑他.
Watch over him!
不客气.
You're welcome.
哇!
背甲龍.
Apceros.
-背甲龍
-好.
- Apceros.
- Yeah.
明白,它们吃草.
Okay. Okay. They eat grass.
水.
Water. Water.
饵.
Bait.
饵?
Bait?
你真有趣.
You're funny.
下次你快要死在沙漠上,
你知道我会对你做什么吗?
Know what I'm gonna do
next time you're dying in the desert?
没什么.
Nothing.
真香.
That smells good.
-捉背甲龍.
-此刻我可以吃些任何东西.
- Catch Cephalos.
- I'll eat anything at this point.
回家.
Home.
是的.
Yeah.
我回家的路.我希望是.
My way home.I hope.
巧克力.
Chocolate.
真美味.
So good.
那是什么?
What's that?
好.
All right.
巧克力.
Chocolate.
不是.
No, no, no.
-巧克力.
-那不是巧克力.
- Chocolate.
- Not chocolate.
发生什么事?
What's going on?
雄火龙.
Rathalos.
你之前说过.什么是雄火龙?
You said that before.
What the hell is a Rathalos?
谢谢.
Thank you.
先别谢我.
Don't thank me yet.
好看吗?
Enjoying the show?
This one must have come from the sky.
什么?
What?
那是什么?
What is that?
帕里柯.
Palico.
我的朋友说我可能误判你.
My friend tells me I misjudged you.
我甚至欠你一个道歉.
I may even owe you an apology.
但是别指望.
Just don't hold your breath.
为何锁住我?
Why did you put me in chains?
你怕什么?
What are you so afraid of?
你的世界...
Your world...
和它可能破坏我的世界.
and what it could do to mine.
你不是第一个从你的世界过来的人.
You aren't the first to cross over
from your world.
还有其他人,
There were others.
在很久以前.
Long time ago.
所以你学会了说我的语言?
That's how you speak my language?
我研究过.
I made a study of it.
我发生了什么事?
What happened to me?
我怎么来到这里?
How did I get here?
我相信我们要找的答案在这里.
I believe that the answers
we both seek lie here.
天塔在那山峰上.
At the peak of that mountain lies
the Sky Tower.
一个古老文明的遗迹.
Remnants of an ancient civilization.
非常先进.非常危险.
Very advanced. Very dangerous.
传说古人懂得穿梭两个世界.
It is said that the Ancients knew
how to travel between both worlds.
我相信那是天塔的用途.
I believe that is the purpose
of the Sky Tower.
所以我带你来这里.
That is what brought you here.
这古文明发生了什么事?
What happened
to this ancient civilization?
他们毁灭了自己.他们的科技害死他们.
They destroyed themselves.
Their technology turned on them.
你认为我的世界跟它有关?
You think my world had something
to do with it.
我怀疑.
I suspect.
但是我们两个世界之间的门户
曾经是个灾难.
But an open gateway between our two worlds
was catastrophic once.
我不容许它再次发生.
I intend to make sure
that doesn't happen again.
我们在调查天塔的途中
We were on our way
to investigate the Sky Tower
当我们遇上角龙.
when we strayed into the Diablos.
我就是在那时候失去了我这位朋友.
That's where I lost my friend here.
治理伤者和修船是我们的优先工作.
Tending to the wounded and repairing
the ship was our first priority.
但是现在,我们要继续我们的任务.
But now we resume our mission.
古人用最凶残的生物
来守护他们的科技...
The Ancients would guard their technology
with the most fearsome of creatures,
一只雄火龙.
a Rathalos.
几乎不可能被杀.
Almost impossible to kill.
它们唯一的弱点是在喷火之前.
Their only weakness is
just before they breathe fire.
你和我们一起战斗...
You help us with the battle ahead,
也许我们可以送你回家.
perhaps we can help you get home.
怎么啦?
What's the matter?
你的世界没猫吗?
You don't have cats in your world?
嘿!
Hey!
你又喝我的杯?
You been drinking from my mug again?
我们在早上出发.
We leave at dawn.
别让我等.
And don't keep me waiting.
我讨厌等待.
I hate waiting.
怎样?
So?
你准备好了吗?
You ready?
我们有很斜的山要爬.
We got a hard climb ahead of us.
走吧!
Come on!
我们相信熔岩热量推动塔内的机器.
We believe that the lava powers
the machinery within the tower.
它控制风暴.
It's controlling the storm.
正是.
Exactly.
它制造通往你的世界的入口...
It's creating a gateway to your world,
但是它看起来不稳定.
but it looks unstable.
走吧.
Let's go.
It's glass.
Estas bone Rathalos.
雄火龙.
Rathalos.
准备好.
Prepare yourself.
记住,它们在喷火前很弱.
Remember, they're weak
just before they breathe fire.
嘿,丑八怪!
Hey, ugly!
没事!你安全了!
It's okay! It's okay.
You're safe now!
叫医护来!
Get the medic!
[阿蒂米斯娜塔莉]
阿蒂米斯队长?
Captain Artemis?
抬她进去里面!
Let's get her inside!
抬起来!
Up!
快走!
Let's go! Let's go!
队长.我们一直在找你.
Captain, we've been searching for you.
她穿着什么衣服?
What the hell is she wearing?
主猎鹰,这是红狼.
Falcon Main, this is Red Wolf.
我们找到黑星了.
We've made contact with Dark Star.
有一名生还者.
We have a lone survivor.
我重复,一名生还者.
I say again, a lone survivor.
-地面部队正在防守周边范围.
-收到,红狼.
-Ground forces are securing the area.
-Copy that, Red Wolf.
队长.
Captain.
你听到我吗?
Can you hear me?
队长?
Captain?
阿蒂米斯队长?
Captain Artemis?
你的其他队员在哪里?
Where are the rest of your men?
-我的人吗?
-是的.
- My men?
- Yes.
A队的其他成员呢?
Where are the rest of Alpha Team?
收到.
Copy that.
我们被袭击!
We're under attack!
瞄准腹部!
Aim for the belly!
雄火龙.
A Rathalos.
装弹!
Load!
开火!
Fire!
不!
No! No!
No!
它朝我们的方向!
It's coming right for us!
闪避!
Evade!
好.
We're on Channel 5. Interference is...
[禁止踩踏]
我的天.
My God.
快来!
Come on!
我解决你了.
I got you.
我的朋友.
My friend.
Thought you might need a little help.
我还是不明白你.
Yeah, I...
still don't understand you, man.
啊,是的.
Oh, yeah.
Friends.
好,谢谢你.
Yeah, thank you.
Min misa chocolate?
我没有巧克力了.
I don't have any more chocolate.
脑筋转快点.
Think fast.
-你来了.
-我们来帮忙.
- You're here.
- We came to help.
我们不能让我们的世界的怪物
袭击你的世界.
We can't have monsters from my world
attacking yours.
又开始了.
It's starting again.
我们没什么时间.
We don't have much time.
将会有另一次袭击.
There's going to be another attack.
我们必须回去.
We have to get back.
我们必须关闭天塔.
We have to shut the Sky Tower down.
让我们先熬过这一关.
Let's try to live through this first.
收到.
Copy that.
来吧!
《怪物猎人》
改编自卡普电玩"怪物猎人"
字幕翻译：
Rachel Yap